Moin Hussain Moti

Room 82 OBH (Palash Nivas). IIIT-Hvderabad. Gachibowli. Hvderabad. India. PINCODE: 500032

🛮 (+91) 9460630274 | 🗷 moin.moti@research.iiit.ac.in | 🐐 www.moinmoti.com | 🤝 moinmoti | 🕤 moinmoti | 🥱 Moin Hussain Moti

Summary_

Research Scholar at Internatinal Institute Of Information Techonology, Hyderabad. Interested in learning new technologies and frameworks, and experienced in building real-life applications combining prominent features of various systems. Research interests include Blockchains, Artificial Intelligence and Game Theory. Enjoys customizing and trying various Linux OS(s) and open-source applications.

Education

International Institute of Information Technology, Hyderabad

CGPA: 8.6

B.Tech + M.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering

July 2015 - June. 2020

- Recipient of Research Award for the Academic Year 2018-19
- Included in the prestigious Dean's List for the semester of Fall 15-16

Publications

FaRM: Fair Reward Mechanism for Information Aggregation in Spontaneous Localized Settings

Full Paper

Moin Hussain Moti, Dimitris Chatzopoulos, Pan Hui, Sujit Gujar

August 2019

Proceedings of the Twenty-Eighth International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI). Pages 506-512. Civic Crowdfunding for Agents with Negative Valuations and Agents with Asymmetric Beliefs

Full Paper

SANKARSHAN DAMLE, MOIN HUSSAIN MOTI, PRAPHUL CHANDRA, SUJIT GUJAR

August 2019

Proceedings of the Twenty-Eighth International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI). Pages 208-214.

Aggregating Citizen Preferences for Public Projects Through Civic Crowdfunding

Short Paper

SANKARSHAN DAMLE, MOIN HUSSAIN MOTI, PRAPHUL CHANDRA, SUJIT GUJAR

May 2019

Proceedings of the 18th International Conference on Autonomous Agents and MultiAgent Systems (AAMAS). Pages 1919-1921.

Work Experience_

Symlab, Hong Kong University of Science and Techonology (HKUST)

Hong Kong

RESEARCH INTERN

May 2018 - July 2018

- Performed an extensive literature survey of existing Information Aggregation (IA) Mechanisms, which included identifying all relevant characteristics of any IA mechanisms and distinguishing all existing mechanisms based on the characteristics.
- · Formulated a new settings, called Spontaneous Localized Settings (SLS), where location specific queries are answered spontaneously.
- · Defined fairness in reward distribution with respect to SLS and devised a new IA mechanism for SLS, where all agents are rewarded fairly.

Symlab, Hong Kong University of Science and Techonology (HKUST)

Hong Kong

RESEARCH INTERN

June 2019 - Aug. 2019

- · Designed a protocol for secure and private information aggregation using inherent blockchain properties
- Developed an Ethereum Decentralized Application (DApp) on Android Framework to implement the above protocol.

Internatinal Institute of Information Techonology, Hyderabad

Hyderabad, India

TEACHING ASSISTANT

August 2017 - May 2019

- Introduction to Game Theory (Spring 2018-19)
- Distributed Trust and Blockchains (Fall 2018-19, Spring 2017-18)
- Operating Systems (Fall 2017-18)

Projects

Gift Hunt

Ultimate Tic Tac Toe

Block in the Hole PC Game

A 3D game similar to BLOXORG with multiple levels and soundtrack.

C++, OpenGL

Short Animated Movie

A short animated movie based on an interaction between father and son.

Unity, C#

CLASH

Interative Shell

An interactive and customized Bash-like shell implemented in C.

C, Bash

Al Bot

A 4x4x4 tic-tac-toe bot made by using Minimax alpha beta pruning.

Python

SEPTEMBER 22, 2019 MOIN HUSSAIN MOTI · RÉSUMÉ